Giuseppe 'Crowind' De Frenza Game Programmer

☑ crowind.gdev@gmail.com | Im GiuseppeDeFrenza | J +39 340 9451877 | 🏠 Pisa, Italy

Profile



Born in Pisa, 1994

After getting my computer science degree I decided to focus on videogame development. I joined the TheSign Comics and Arts Academy in 2018, from where I graduated in september 2021 with full marks.

My favourite fields are Shaders and Code Architecture, but during my career I have been able to learn a lot in multiple fields, like Artificial Intelligence, Procedural Animations, Procedural Generation, and Tool Programming.

I have always tried to be versatile: I extend tools and libraries when needed and I do extensive researches prior to implementing new algorithms or structures. I also have basic skills in 2D art and game design.

Education

Università di Pisa Bachelor degree in Computer Science, 99/110 TheSign Comics & Art Academy | Event Horizon

Game Programming, 30L/30

Pisa, Italy Sept 2013 - May 2019

Firenze

Sept 2018 - Sept 2021

Projects

Roll with the Tiles | *Solo Project* | *C#, Unity* Vampire Nights | Shaders | hlsl, Unity **Lost in the Unknown** | *Programming, Design* | *C#, hlsl, Unity* **Beyond Machines** | *Programming*, *Design* | *C#*, *Unity* Re-Pair | GGJ2020 | Programming | C#, hlsl, Unity A Back of Gold | IFGJ2019 | Programming | C#, Unity

June 2020 - Current June 2021 - Sept 2021 Nov 2019 - Current Nov 2018 - July 2019 Jan 2020 Sept 2019

Skills

Human Languages: Italian, English (C1 Grade B)

Languages: C/C++, C#/F#, hlsl, HTML/CSS, Java, LaTeX

Frameworks: Unity, Unreal Engine

Developer Tools: Git, JetBrains Rider, Visual Studio, Adobe Photoshop, Vegas Pro, FMOD Studio

Unity Assets: Rewired, Amplify Shader Editor, Behavior Designer, Odin, DOTween

Work Experience

Office assistant, Handyman

2019 - 2021

Lucca Manga School

Lucca, part-time

Task included were: Video Editing, Social Media Management, Mail Management, Database Management.

Extracurriculars

Fighting Game Community Contributions

2015 - Current

ToSmash - Super Smash Bros. Toscana

- Contributed to the organization of more than 100 Super Smash Bros. for WiiU and Super Smash Bros. Ultimate offline tournaments
- Designed the whole entirety of graphic products (*Power Rankings, Streaming Layouts, Advertising, Logo*)

Rivals of Aether Italia

- · Contributed to the organization of more than 50 Rivals of Aether online tournaments
- Designed numerous graphic products (Power Rankings, Advertising)

Super Smash Bros. Italia

• Designed Power Rankings for Winter 2017/2018, Spring 2018 and Fall 2018

Misc.

- Italian and English tournament commentary
- · Community management

Hobbies

- I'm an avid player of tabletop games, especially strategic games like Brass, Concordia or Scythe.
- I've played guitar and other instruments for years, I also recorded a short album with a video-game soundtracks cover band!
- I greatly enjoy casual hiking since I was a child! Looking for chestnuts, raspberries and blackberries also makes the hiking experience precious to me.
- I'm a huge birds lover, especially crows, ravens and parrots.